so I grew up and kept on next to an
所以我长大了，继续靠近
Italian family so we were a German
意大利家庭，所以我们是德国人
family mixed in Italian family and we
家庭混在意大利家庭，我们
got on really well except there was one
相处得很好，除了有一个
day we we didn't like them very much
那天我们不是很喜欢他们
no 1982 July the live but besides that
没有1982年7月的直播，但除此之外
we got on very well so let's have a look
我们相处得很好，让我们来看一下
at Java names string Oh missile is here
在Java的名字字符串哦导弹在这里
we've got a little way in which we
我们有一些方法
convert an int to a string and the
将int转换为字符串，然后
question is which is the best way what
问题是最好的方法是什么
jdk that's a good question was it what
jdk这是一个好问题，是什么
Teddy K good question section where it
泰迪K好问题节在哪里
was
原为
okay so one way is you can just do the
好的，一种方法是您可以
lazy way double quotes plus the well
懒惰的方式双引号加井号
which of course you should never do
你当然不应该做
because you shouldn't be lazy as a
因为你不应该像一个人一样懒惰
programmer the other one is if your to
程序员另一个是如果你要
string others interests of value of the
串连他人的价值利益
in string that value of an integer of
在字符串中，整数值为
Kate integer so who sees the first is
凯特整数，所以谁看到第一个是
the fastest way let's say Java 12 let's
最快的方法比方说Java 12
take cyclocross why not
为什么不骑自行车
are you have used other 12 okay who sees
你是否使用过其他12个人，
a second this faster who see it's a
一秒钟更快，谁看到它是
third as a fastest way to do it it's
第三，这是最快的方法
gonna be somebody saying a third okay
有人说第三点好
pretty thank you
非常感谢你
this is a fourth is faster okay we're
这是第四快，好吧，我们
getting a bit warmer classy and the
变得有点优雅，而
fifth one first one okay very good
第五个，第一个，很好
and another one another city question
还有另一个城市的问题
these are all silly questions just to
这些都是愚蠢的问题
get us thinking but and which is the
让我们思考，但这是
fastest way to append strings together
将字符串附加在一起的最快方法
so the first one I am I'm using plus
所以我正在使用的第一个
which of course is the can't be fastest
当然哪个不能最快
because it's shortest false code has to
因为它是最短的错误代码
be long of a bus the second one I'm
我第二辆公交车很长
making a string builder and I'm sure if
做一个字符串生成器，我确定
you've worked with code long enough
您已经使用了足够长的代码
you've seen code like that and the third
您已经看到了类似的代码
one you see the things when you a string
一串就看到了
builder you're you're making new char s
生成器，您正在制作新字符
all the time so the third one we have
所有的时间，所以我们有第三个
first working out how big is the array
首先算出数组有多大
is supposed to be and then we we add all
应该是然后我们添加所有
the strings together so who says the
弦在一起，谁说
first is the fastest okay which trade
首先是最快的行吗
okay okay
好吧好吧
anything after Java 7 Java 7 and
Java 7之后的所有内容Java 7和
afterwards who says the first is a
后来谁说第一个是
fastest okay who says the second is a
最快的好，谁说第二个是
fastest okay good very good
最快还可以很好很好
who do you say it's a third is the
你说谁是三分之一
fastest okay now who didn't put up their
现在最快，没放他们的
hand anybody didn't program please what
手有人没有编程请
granda
格兰达
okay you're right thank you so though
好吧，你是对的，尽管如此
all the same exactly the same and the
都是一样的
reason they're the same it's because I
他们一样的原因是因为我
won't tell you I will tell you later
不会告诉你，我稍后再告诉你
okay now I want to go back to history
好吧，现在我想回到历史
when the dinosaurs roamed the earth Java
恐龙在地上漫游时
hundreds era okay and in those days they
几百个世纪还可以
actually starts by saying private cha Lu
其实从说私人查鲁开始
square brackets you know these were C
方括号，你知道这些是C
programmers and in those days when their
程序员，在那个时候
hash code that was bigger than 16
大于16的哈希码
characters they made samples of it so
他们制作了角色的样本
basically looked at every X number of
基本上看着每X个
characters so no sorry
字符，所以不后悔
that's one way that it looked a tiny I
那是它看起来很小的一种方式
think 30 characters off their course I
我认为他们偏离了30个字符
sample off all the strings and it was
采样所有的字符串，这是
obviously not very it wasn't very good
显然不是很好，不是很好
hash code at the end because if it
末尾的哈​​希码，因为如果
several big strings they would be have
他们将拥有几个大弦
almost very very similar hash curves or
几乎非常相似的哈希曲线或
the same hash codes and some other
相同的哈希码和其他一些
things like equals didn't check of
等于等的东西没有检查
objects we were actually the same
我们实际上是相同的对象
internet aesthetic hash table which
互联网美学哈希表
happened to be a memory and a string
碰巧是一个记忆和一个字符串
buffer was basically a modifiable string
缓冲区基本上是可修改的字符串
safe version that you could use for
您可以使用的安全版本
changing once you had constructed it now
一旦构造好就改变
when you call to string on the chart on
当您在图表上调用字符串时
the string buffer what was really cool
字符串缓冲区真的很棒
with that was that it she'd the same
就是因为她是一样的
underlying chareth so we didn't have a
基本的慈善组织，所以我们没有
new char a being made every time we call
每次调用都会产生新的字符
to string so this was some of the magic
串起来，所以这是一些魔术
that happens brilliant I mean if you
那真是太好了，我的意思是如果你
look at the way that the source code if
看一下源代码的方式
you look at the Java source code
您看一下Java源代码
nowadays you will see that in the Java
如今，您将在Java中看到这一点
source code when you say to string it
您说要串起来的原始码
makes a new array every time we call it
每次调用它都会创建一个新数组
we'll get back to that in a moment
我们待会儿再讲
this is what the hash code looked like
这是哈希代码的样子
had streamed up 11.0 you can see that if
已经流了11.0，您可以看到，如果
the length is less than 16 and it
长度小于16并且
actually adds up the numbers as a
实际上将这些数字加起来
multiplier otherwise it looks at only
乘数，否则它只看
eight of the characters
八个字符
it says the skippers length divided by
它说船长除以
eight so at index of eight of the code
在代码的八个索引处是八个
so if you have 1,000 characters it only
所以如果你有1000个字符
looks at eight of them to work out a
看着他们八个来解决
hash code and the bad way this is
哈希码，这是不好的方式
demetri demetri demetri is a
demetri demetri是一个
soft engineer he's our chief
软工程师，他是我们的负责人
troublemaker disorganized @j creep he
麻烦制造者杂乱无章的@j爬行他
was trying not to come he tried to he
试图不来他试图
tells me that he he hurt his his leg
告诉我他伤了腿
skiing but actually last night he got
滑雪，但实际上昨晚他
beaten up because he asked for Hawaiian
殴打，因为他要夏威夷
pizza yes this is high in ski boots the
披萨是的，这是滑雪靴的高度
troublemaker the creator which a Cretan
麻烦制造者的克里特岛
con from Java specialist newsletter and
Java专家通讯和
will try to entertain you with this
会尝试以此来招待你
string he's three yeah yeah so just by
弦，他是三个，是的，只是
the way if you're not there to please
如果你不在那儿请
join also I've got I've got a surprise
加入也有惊喜
gift which will sort of not work after
礼物在以后将不起作用
7:00 tonight so if you look at that
今晚7:00，所以如果你看看
after 7:00 you'll get a not so a big
7:00之后，您将获得不那么大的收益
surprise gift if you did before 7:00
如果您在7:00之前做过惊喜礼物
you'll get a big surprise gift but
你会得到一个很大的惊喜礼物，但是
office ever won't be as great
办公室永远不会像以前那么伟大
so that tinier old Vox will mmm ro 19
以便小巧的老Vox会把ROM改为19
have a look at that if you want you'll
看一下，如果你想
get something if you do the links also
如果您也做链接，也可以得到一些东西
here the on the side as I said it's a
我说的这边是
changes off to save them tonight you
改变以保存他们今晚你
know once the beer starts the gift
知道一旦啤酒开始礼物
diminishes significantly so Drive
大幅减少，因此云端硬盘
wondered wonder changed things of it
想知道奇迹改变了它的事情
first of all the the field stay the same
首先，该领域保持不变
but an hashcode was still sampling they
但是哈希码仍在采样
they moved the intern to to some native
他们将实习生转移到一些本地人
code which wasn't necessarily going to
不一定要去的代码
be better than Java
比Java更好
and yeah so all sorts of weird stuff
是的，所以各种各样的怪异事物
like chopper case had some weird edge
像菜刀案有一些奇怪的边缘
cases like the German SF became too big
德国SF之类的案件变得太大了
big asses so so the lethal stream could
大屁股，所以致命的流可以
change we needed to uppercase and kind
改变我们需要大写和亲切
of weird in traveler wonder to the field
旅行者奇怪的领域
stayed the same but they changed the
保持不变，但他们改变了
hashcode
哈希码
and that was the last time there dared
那是那里最后一次胆敢
to do that because the backlash you
这样做是因为你的强烈反对
can't imagine even one or two they were
无法想象他们曾经是一两个
reading so much legacy code out there
在那里读了很多旧代码
and people like my user cysts are not
像我的使用者囊肿这样的人不是
working anymore you know your dues
工作了，你知道你应得的
martin was talking about about crybabies
马丁在谈论哭泣婴儿
a lot of crybabies in those days and so
那时有很多婴儿
what did it was they instead of counting
他们是做什么的，而不是数数
only eight characters they added up all
他们只将八个字符加起来
the characters and it broke a bunch of
人物，它打破了一堆
tests which was probably not such a bad
测试可能还不错
thing
事情
also they add the comparable interface
他们还添加了可比的界面
and we'll get back to that a little bit
我们会回到一点
later what that means now the
后来这意味着现在
performance in the past was constant
过去的表现是不变的
time performance so it didn't matter how
时间表现，所以没关系
big the the the string was it took the
大的字符串是花了
same amount of time in constant time not
在恒定时间内的相同时间量不是
the same but constant to calculate the
相同但不变的计算
the asylum there the hashcode wears a
那里的哈希码戴着一个庇护
change to linear time now of course we
当然，现在更改为线性时间
all know what that means it can become
所有人都知道这意味着它会变成
significant is slower to calculate the
显着性计算速度较慢
hash and so the book was written and
哈希，所以这本书是写的，
called the driver performance an idiot
称驾驶员表现为白痴
guide know the idiom the idiom guide
引导了解成语引导成语
idiom guide right here you know it was a
成语指南就在这里，你知道这是一个
good book when they wrote it it was but
他们写的好书是
performance books they they've got a
他们有一个表演书
shelf life of about three months right
保质期约三个月吧
until the next job version comes out and
直到出现下一个作业版本
then there you can you can throw them
然后在那里你可以扔他们
away it's a problem they wrote a good
他们写的很好是一个问题
book but in sort of one of the biggest
书，但有点像最大的书
arguments in the book was you should
书中的论点是你应该
always cash your hash code so you must
总是兑现您的哈希码，所以您必须
must never use string as a hash code it
绝不能使用字符串作为哈希码
was have to put string inside an object
不得不在对象中放入字符串
and then catch the hash code and shortly
然后赶上哈希码，不久
after the wrote the book Java 3 came out
在写了《 Java 3》这本书之后
and they cashed the hash code right now
他们现在兑现了哈希码
the thing is that the idea was caching
事实是这个想法在缓存
the hash code doesn't actually help us
哈希码实际上并没有帮助我们
that often in many cases because the
在许多情况下通常是因为
whole point of a map is to put things in
地图的整个重点是将事物放入
which you can get back later so you put
你可以稍后再回来，所以你把
in the value you throw away the key and
在价值中，您丢掉了钥匙，
later on when you know what the object
以后当你知道对象是什么
back again you regenerate the key and
再次返回，您重新生成密钥并
you find the value again that's sort of
您会再次发现该值
hard map works it's used um and and if
硬地图可以使用um，如果
you look at this here I'm I've got hash
你在这里看这个，我是哈希
table which takes a hundred milliseconds
花费一百毫秒的表
just to make it really slow and actually
只是让它变得缓慢而实际上
the amount of time it takes to put
投入的时间
thirty elements and get them there's
三十个元素，让它们在那里
exactly the same with you cash will not
与您完全一样的现金不会
cash the key the three directors make it
兑现三位董事兑现的钥匙
does make a difference because inside
确实有所作为，因为里面
the hash marks gonna catch anyone the
井号将抓住任何人
the action hash code value so it really
操作哈希码值，所以它真的
doesn't prove that much but anyway they
没有证明那么多，但无论如何他们
added this this thing called the hash
添加了这个叫做哈希的东西
and what was interesting is at the time
当时有趣的是
the the memory for that hash was free
该哈希的内存是免费的
okay on a 32-bit machine at least
至少在32位计算机上还可以
because the the value was a char array
因为该值是一个char数组
and that's four bytes the point two to
这是四个字节，指向第二点
the Troy was four bytes then int is four
Troy是四个字节，然后int是四个
bytes offset the opposite accountant has
对方会计师具有的字节偏移
use of four bytes and it indicates
使用四个字节，它指示
anyway in multiples of eight therefore
因此无论如何以八的倍数
it basically was for free having put in
基本上是免费的
s in those day and of course depending
在那一天，当然取决于
on what you're running on its 32-bit
在您的32位元上执行
64-bit copies Cobras oops or not it'll
眼镜蛇的64位副本会失败
make a difference but in those days was
有所作为，但在那些日子里
issued for free and you know we hope we
免费发行，您知道我们希望我们
all know that string is immutable in
都知道字符串在
fact even say that the documentation it
事实上甚至说文件
actually does change of the hash
实际上改变了哈希
internally when you when you call hash
内部，当您调用哈希时
code it changes it into your state it's
代码将其更改为您的状态
not visible from outside and it's it's a
从外面看不到，这是一个
data race which is a benign dare to race
数据竞赛，这是一个良性的竞赛
because the the Roth will be the same no
因为罗斯会是一样的
matter how many times call it so the the
不管多少次，所以
is a day to race but it doesn't matter
是比赛的一天，但没关系
because in the end the value is still
因为最终价值仍然是
going to be 42 so it doesn't matter
将会是42，所以没关系
which way you call it now look at these
现在用哪种方式来看这些
strings this is some Ukrainian which
串这是一些乌克兰人
I've found some it's it's it's a it's
我发现一些是它是
it's a 10-4 directory from the Ukraine
这是乌克兰的10-4目录
right so hungry hunk units too short the
对，所以饥饿的大块头单位太短了
names are too short so what do these
名字太短了，这些怎么办
things have in common the hash code is
哈希码的共同点是
zero right so the hash code is always
右为零，因此哈希码始终为
zero each of these strings the hash code
将这些字符串中的每个字符串归零
is zero and if I don't know how I found
是零，如果我不知道如何找到
them well okay there isn't algorithm
他们很好，没有算法
that somebody wrote contramar than that
有人写了相反的话
food was somebody really famous and I
食物真的很出名，我
don't remove his name now so it's really
现在不要删除他的名字，所以
no it was more reinholt I think I think
不，那是更多的回味，我想
it was mark Reinhold
那是马克·莱因霍尔德
somebody really famous wrote an
真正有名的人写了
algorithm where he he reversed a hash
他反转哈希的算法
code so if you want to have a hash code
代码，所以如果您想使用哈希代码
of 25 you say I want the penny father
25个你说我想要一分钱的父亲
then
然后
generates a string for you with the
为您生成一个字符串
hashcode 25 per simply going in reverse
哈希码25，只需反向执行
to get to the hashcode so so I tried
进入哈希码，所以我尝试了
using the algorithm to generate strings
使用算法生成字符串
but the problem is it will give you a
但问题是它会给你一个
string with those with a number but I
与那些带数字的弦，但我
wanted to find lots of strings with the
想用
hash code of zero so I just stood at
哈希码为零，所以我只是站在
brute force are apologized but it did
蛮力道歉，但确实如此
work an end to the brute force and so
尽力消除暴力，等等
here and the limbs in smoothly with
在这里和四肢顺利
these strings is they all have hash code
这些字符串都是散列代码
of zero and if I add them together
零，如果我将它们加在一起
anyone to any two together even the same
任何人到任何两个在一起，甚至相同
one together the hash code is ginn zero
哈希码为1，则ginn为零
because once you get a 0 you can you
因为一旦你得到0，你就可以
start from the beginning to get back to
从头开始回到
zero so the interesting thing with that
零，所以有趣的是
is because they thought the hash code of
是因为他们认为
zero any combination of these strings
将这些字符串的任何组合归零
also gives you hash to the zero and
还可以让您将哈希值归零
let's have a look at why that is so bad
让我们来看看为什么这么糟糕
I'm going to look at different versions
我要看不同的版本
of Java and let's go back to the how do
Java，让我们回到如何做
you eat so my neighbors in South Africa
你吃饭所以我在南非的邻居
were a little bit shorter than the
比...短一点
German neighbors and so I see why this
德国邻居，所以我明白了为什么
is so low here and it's trying to get
在这里太低了，它试图
this is working okay so here's the code
这很好，所以这是代码
that's before and it's basically I've
那是以前，基本上是我
got the zero hash codes and the zero
得到零散列码和零
hash codes just to feel the strings and
哈希码只是为了感觉字符串和
then I simply combine them together like
然后我简单地将它们组合在一起
you can you can have an infinite number
你可以拥有无​​限个
of almost exchange generated in fact
实际上产生的几乎交换
practically generated with hash code of
实际上是用的哈希码生成的
zero so and so what I'm going to do is
零，所以我要做的是
I'm going to run this first of all with
我将首先使用
Java 6 okay and here's a as you see as I
Java 6好的，这是我看到的
double the number of off strings and
关闭字符串的数量加倍，并且
it's actually not that many and every
实际上并不是那么多
time I make it twice as much the the
时间我使它的两倍
speed gets also approximately twice as
速度也大约是
slow so you can see that the hash the
慢，所以您可以看到哈希
hash code lookup so we look from about
哈希码查找，所以我们从
one second to about two seconds those
一秒到两秒左右
are the roughly the Oh rod about so and
大概是这样的哦棒
so what you can say is that this this
所以你可以说的是
actually the hash
实际上是哈希
look up there the hashcode so to find
查找哈希码，以便找到
the value even though the hashcode is
该值，即使哈希码是
cached ends up being being being linear
缓存最终是线性的
now the problem with is not that the
现在的问题不是
hash code is cashed in lost cash the
哈希码以现金丢失的形式兑现
problem is that all of the strings end
问题是所有字符串都结束了
up in the same bucket inside the hash
在哈希内的同一存储桶中
map but that's why we end up with a
地图，但这就是为什么我们最终得到一个
linear look up and it's going from the
线性查找，它是从
hash map degrades the linked list right
哈希图会降低链表的权限
in Java 6 now something went wrong
在Java 6中现在出了点问题
probably we exceeded some size where
可能我们超出了某个尺寸
things are not not happy anymore but
事情不再快乐了，但是
it's generally going to be linear now um
现在通常会是线性的
in Java 7 they actually did something
在Java 7中，他们实际上做了一些事情
which was quite interesting and they
这很有趣，他们
they wanted to stop this from happening
他们想阻止这种情况的发生
they wanted to stop its people from
他们想阻止它的人
attacking web servers by sending the
通过发送攻击网络服务器
same string over sensory multiple
感官倍数相同的字符串
strings was all over hash code of zero
字符串全部为零的哈希码
and then summer ended up in astonishment
然后夏天变得惊讶
when we do cookie greater the hash brown
当我们做饼干更大的哈希布朗
and so as we saw with with with this
正如我们所看到的
with Java 6 it became a problem now Java
Java 6成为现在的一个问题
for now of course I don't have Java 3
现在我当然没有Java 3
arm our machine and Java for the fields
为现场武装我们的机器和Java
of the same as 2 over 3 and they they
等于2超过3，他们
and introduced such a sequence interface
并介绍了这样的序列接口
so that you could either speak to draw a
这样您就可以讲话画一个
sequence or to string and also had
序列或字符串，也有
regular expressions which are not all
不是全部的正则表达式
sort of the fastest you talked a bit
你说得最快的那种
about that I think when we get to the
关于这一点，我认为当我们到达
format maybe mention that now of course
格式可能现在提到
in the past when he added strings
在过去，当他添加字符串
together like hello class Arg 0 it would
就像你好类Arg 0一样
generate a string buffer and they pulled
产生一个字符串缓冲区，他们拉
our paint alert on a pin dogs note got
我们的狗狗便条上的油漆警报得到了
to string and this new string buffer
到字符串和这个新的字符串缓冲区
would would in the Java code make an
将在Java代码中使
array of 16 characters in Java 5 the
Java 5中16个字符的数组
fields of Santa's job or not 3 but the
圣诞老人的工作领域与否3但
mark them final except for the hash
将其标记为最终值（散列除外）
which you know one should always try and
您知道应该始终尝试并
mark fields final where you can and they
将字段标记为最终位置，它们会
had code points so a character could
有代码点，所以角色可以
actually be a combination of two
实际上是两者的结合
characters also we had sort of the
字符，我们也有点
string builder which was a
字符串生成器
unsynchronized version
非同步版本
off the string buffer and and the char
关闭字符串缓冲区和char
array would no longer be shared with
数组将不再与之共享
with created streets now the thing is
现在有了创建的街道
that when we went from Java for taught
当我们从Java传授
Java fibrates who actually recompile the
实际重新编译Java Java的人
code to take advantage of this of this
代码来利用这个
new new feature I actually at one point
我实际上有一个新的新功能
I was working with the library and and
我当时在图书馆工作，并且
and I changed the string plus with just
我改变了字符串加上
normal plus appending to use string
普通加附加使用字符串
buffers with the preset size because it
具有预设大小的缓冲区，因为它
did make the noticeable difference in
确实在
the performance so I shared that about
表演，所以我分享了
10%
10％
I made it by 10% faster with that
我的速度快了10％
optimization when it went back into our
回到我们的优化
before so the problem is that
之前的问题是
optimization actually wouldn't work
优化实际上是行不通的
Java five hundreds because North no
JAVA五百，因为北没有
longer string buffer it's doing bullet
更长的字符串缓冲区正在做子弹
so you actually had to go back and
所以你实际上不得不回去
change in stream buffers of string
更改字符串流缓冲区
builders and recompile or it hurt okay
建设者并重新编译，否则就没事了
Java six nothing much change in the
Java 6没什么大变化
structure but that did add the speech of
结构，但这确实增加了
compressed strings we sometimes a sting
压缩的弦我们有时会刺痛
would use a char array and other times
将使用char数组和其他时间
of byte array as as a foundation where
以字节数组为基础
and for the for keeping the characters
为了保持角色
which was kind of weird if you work with
如果和你一起工作，那有点奇怪
reflection and you look at the string
反射，你看着琴弦
and sometimes it's uh bitrates I was the
有时是比特率，我是
char array the things got funky they
字符数组东西变得时髦
also added optimized stinking cat at
还添加了优化的臭猫
some Java six version and which meant
一些Java 6版本，这意味着
that your char a could could at that
你的字符可以在那
would also be shared between your string
也将在您的字符串之间共享
buffer string build and string so
缓冲字符串构建和字符串等
remember when we when I first showed
记得我们第一次表演的时候
I've wanted zero that they they shared
我想要他们分享的零
the char array between the string but
字符串之间的char数组，但是
from the string that happens
从发生的字符串
automatically from Java 6 onwards so if
从Java 6开始自动
you look at the Java code it doesn't
你看看它的Java代码
happen but in the real world that does
发生，但在现实世界中确实如此
happen so that that's quite cool here's
发生，所以这很酷
some so the first benchmark we were
有些是我们的第一个基准
adding only strings together I mean
我只将字符串加在一起
you're only adding strings together it
你只是把弦加在一起
doesn't matter which which way you do it
不管采用哪种方式都可以
it's exactly the same speed so when you
速度完全一样所以当你
look at these values the the pain basic
看这些价值观的痛苦基本
is that was this with plus the pain
就是这样加上痛苦
string is with
字符串与
a stringbuilder and a pin stringbuilder
一个stringbuilder和一个pin stringbuilder
of the size you notice that they create
您注意到它们创建的大小
the same number of bytes hundred eight
相同数量的字节一百八十八
bytes Java seven hundred bytes Java
字节Java七百字节Java
eight hundred bytes 12 11 100 20 bytes
800字节12 11 100 20字节
we'll talk more but Java level versus
我们将讨论更多，但Java级别与
Java 18 moment and that includes driver
Java 18 moment，其中包括驱动程序
9 as well why that's nice Java 7 I
9以及为什么这很好Java 7我
mentioned in that day that they were
在那天提到他们
concerned about these the plus will
关注这些加号
attack on on servers by having lots lots
通过大量攻击服务器
of strings of hash code of zero so they
哈希码为零的字符串，因此它们
solved that by having but by by having
通过拥有但通过拥有
another hash code int it's a called hash
另一个哈希码int这就是所谓的哈希
32 now when I saw that I was got really
32现在当我看到我真的
excited I thought awesome now all my
兴奋，我现在觉得很棒
systems are going to be faster and and I
系统将变得更快，而我
use it for many years without realizing
使用了很多年却没有意识到
that it doesn't work until new it's
直到新的它才起作用
explicitly turned it on any redundant of
明确地将其打开
supremist talk was like oh it wasn't
至高无上的谈话就像是不是
wasn't never used right so the good
从来没有用过，所以好的
thing with having hash 32 it's still a
具有哈希值32的东西仍然是
linear cost but they use some
线性成本，但他们使用一些
randomization to stop you from being
随机化阻止你成为
able to make always the same hashcode
能够使总是相同的哈希码
and and they default as hash of one not
并且它们默认为一个不的哈希
hash of zero so if it's not initially
零的哈希值，如果不是最初的哈希值
it's gonna be hash of hash of one so
这将是一个哈希的哈希
it's it hops a lot so if you run this
它跳得很多，所以如果你运行这个
with Java 7 they must quickly copy the
使用Java 7，他们必须快速复制
server
服务器
so if we go back to our our test here
所以如果我们回到这里进行测试
run Java 7
运行Java 7
the first version is going to be exactly
第一个版本将完全是
the same as Java 6 also linear
与Java 6一样也是线性的
degradation as we double the size of int
退化，因为我们将int的大小加倍
gets about twice as slow the proximity
接近速度慢一倍
obviously there's some bumps in the road
显然道路上有一些颠簸
but that's sort of what happens and then
但这就是发生的事情，然后
if I if I add the field sorry that that
如果我添加字段，对不起
environment variable then okay let's put
环境变量，然后我们放
this in here now look at the Proms
现在在这里看舞会
because it first gets worse once we can
因为一旦我们可以，它首先变得更糟
over threshold then it starts either
超过阈值则开始
using this in 32 so once it gets past
在32中使用它，所以一旦它过去
256 it uses this in 32 and then it gets
256它在32中使用它，然后得到
bit faster I hope
我希望更快一点
I know I've done something wrong
我知道我做错了
some are still using Java 6 now that the
现在，有些仍在使用Java 6
compiler to the thing issue I am sure
我确定的东西编译器
but I might be to be so using forever 6
但我可能会永远使用6
I may have got the something wrong and
我可能出了点问题，
it's something wrong I don't feel quite
我觉得不太对劲
sure what
确定什么
it's a DMS first person at work and I
这是DMS第一人称的工作，我
shouldn't have to recompile it almost
几乎不必重新编译
certainly not I'm going to recompile it
当然不是，我要重新编译它
just to make sure that no that's I'm not
只是为了确保不，那我不是
gonna do that
要做那个
the threshold oh yeah of course I've got
门槛哦，是的，我当然有
the look I've got different there the
我在那里的外观与众不同
flag in the wrong place so it's simple
标记错误的位置，这很简单
stupidity so it should mean the
愚蠢，所以它应该意味着
beginning so you see what it initially
开始，所以你看到它最初
it runs and then once it once it gets
它运行，然后一旦它得到
past a threshold it really speeds up
超过阈值，它确实加快了速度
right so the the hashmap lookup is no
对，所以哈希表查找为否
longer linear because you don't have a
更长的线性，因为您没有
little linked list off of elements of as
as的元素的很少链接列表
keys but but you had to turn on
键，但您必须打开
explicitly didn't do that didn't have
明确没有做那没有
any of this any of these benefits and
这些好处中的任何一个，以及
again the reason why they didn't want to
再次是他们不想的原因
do automatically is because yet two
自动执行是因为还有两个
people would complain that their tests
人们会抱怨他们的测试
don't work anymore
不再工作了
um alright and also there was another
嗯，还有另一个
constructor which we could abuse which
我们可能滥用的构造函数
made which we passed an array and
使我们通过数组并
boolean and shade now this was a this
布尔值和阴影现在这是一个
this class was as method was was an it
此类是因为方法是
was package access but you could access
是软件包访问权限，但您可以访问
it with shade secrets get java.lang
带有阴影的秘密得到java.lang
access new string unsafe with the char
使用char访问不安全的新字符串
array and that would then hat that
数组，然后会讨厌
wasn't it is the same tray as you pass
是不是和你经过的是同一托盘
in for the string so if you wanted to
在字符串中，所以如果您想
minimize a memory usage you could do
尽量减少您可以使用的内存使用量
that now they've moved that out of
现在他们已经将其移出
harm's way for Java 9 and it wouldn't
Java 9有害的方式，而且不会
really work drama line anywhere because
在任何地方都可以正常使用戏剧，因为
now they're caught by tracing sort of
现在他们被追查到
tourism another thing which that change
旅游业改变的另一件事
was the the substring in the past used
是过去使用的子字符串
to
至
a new string that pointed to the same
指向相同的新字符串
char array but was different it offset
字符数组，但与它不同
and length and that changed that to be a
和长度，并将其更改为
new tire every time which which which
新轮胎每次哪个哪个
caused this is for quite a few companies
导致这是为很多公司
where you can easily get around that by
在这里您可以轻松解决
making your own subbable string but it's
制作自己的小写字符串，但这是
a bit messy so that's but the whole
有点混乱，那只是整个
reason to remove that was to what memory
删除那个的原因是要记什么
leaks if you get the big XML document
如果获取大的XML文档，则泄漏
which is one gigabyte and you take user
这是一千兆字节，您需要用户
ID or something out of it you still have
身份证或其他东西
a pointer to the original array so you
指向原始数组的指针
lick in memory even though you just
舔记忆，即使你只是
think you just have user ID that's was
认为您只有用户ID
the reason to remove by the way jar Java
删除jar Java的原因
is not the only one time that had this
并非只有一次
so v8 for instance from Google
因此，例如来自Google的v8
they had this optimization then they
他们进行了优化，然后
removed it and they put it back because
删除它，他们把它放回去，因为
users complained well JavaScript yes so
用户抱怨很好JavaScript是的
it's it's it's it's ya know nobody can
是的，是的，你知道没人能
be happy with both option you know
对两种选择都满意
something's always gonna complain does
总是会抱怨的事
matter what you do okay
不管你做什么
Java 8 they they've got the value the
Java 8他们拥有的价值
value as a char array and in - the
值作为char数组，并且在-
adrenaline hash 32 again because they
再次肾上腺素哈希32，因为他们
solved the problem with the birther with
解决了出生者的问题
the link with with the linear
与线性链接
performance of a map in a general way
一般地图的性能
and what they do with hash map since
以及自哈希表以来的操作
Java is as soon as you have committee
Java尽您所能
collisions they actually create a binary
碰撞实际上创建了一个二进制文件
tree in order for that to work properly
为了使它正常工作
your key has to be what should be
您的钥匙必须是应该的
comparable this is why since Java 8 you
可比这是为什么从Java 8开始
should always make all keys - code
应该始终进行所有键操作-代码
equals and comparable so that you can
相等且可比，以便您可以
take advantage of the great performance
发挥出色的性能
improvements you have each other 8 going
彼此改善8
forward also you've got top some
向前也有一些顶尖
deduplication of char array so I'll show
char数组的重复数据删除，所以我将展示
you that in a second but I want to run
你一秒钟，但我想跑
that test again with Java 8 so let's go
再次使用Java 8进行测试，让我们开始吧
to Java head
到Java头
provide and this time without any sort
提供，这次没有任何形式
of funny settings straight off a box you
有趣的设置直接在盒子里
can see that as we as we increase the
可以看到随着我们增加
size of map the performance does not
地图尺寸性能不
degrade as badly as it did before and
像以前一样严重退化
here all the elements are still in the
这里所有的元素仍然在
same bucket but it's a binary tree not
同一个桶，但是不是二叉树
so it's it's declaratory grading with
所以它是声明式评分
with order log in or whatever it means
与订单登录或任何意味着
yeah and this behavior you'll see or
是的，您会看到此行为或
some Java eleven as well same top thing
一些Java 11以及同样重要的事情
now of course you were at the DC comic
现在你当然在DC漫画了
desert you lost might be exactly the
你失去的沙漠可能正是
same but you can see the the performance
一样，但是你可以看到表现
is not degrading as badly as number six
表现不如第六名
so so for example for 65,000 you know
因此，例如对于65,000
elements the map in one in one entry we
将地图合二为一的元素
still mean I'm looking doing lots of
仍然意味着我正在做很多事情
lookup not just one look up it's still
查找不仅是查找，还是
performant performance enough now
现在性能足够
deduplication is quite a nice little
重复数据删除相当不错
feature you get this in g1 not in the
功能，您可以在g1中获得此功能，而不是在
other three C's
其他三个C
I don't know why there probably could
我不知道为什么可能
add another one spa but the idea is that
再添加一个水疗中心，但想法是
is that they if you've got multiple
是他们，如果你有多个
strings which have the same content or
具有相同内容的字符串或
they you know they're different strings
他们知道他们是不同的弦
but they've got you know the effort of
但他们让您知道
interest isn't the Creator separately
兴趣不是创造者分开
then before the object gets moved to the
然后在对象移动到
old space it's the the Quattro Reigate
旧空间是Quattro Reigate
shade with other strengths which have
具有其他优势的阴影
the same the same value so here are
相同的值，所以这里是
making two strings with tooth with the
用牙做两根弦
same two are a so it's going to be two
同一两个是一个，所以它将是两个
strings with with different Shara's you
与不同的撒拉的你的字符串
can see it here with reflection and
可以在这里看到它的反射和
printing out get a snort and get this
打印出一个鼻息，并得到这个
one and you can see the Torah that
一个，你可以看到摩西五经
torres are different after the GC is run
GC运行后，炬力有所不同
now I'm quoting explicitly GC it will
现在我明确引用GC，它将
happen even if you don't do that will
即使你不这样做也会发生
still go and undo the deduplication the
仍然可以删除重复数据删除
fourth curse the old space will do that
第四诅咒旧空间会做到这一点
and afterwards you'll see that it's now
然后您会看到现在
there's the same char a so this can save
有一个相同的字符，所以可以节省
your memory without any real efforts
没有任何实际努力的记忆
well it it will it should it usually
好吧，它应该通常吗
does from our C make things a little bit
从我们的C中得到的东西使事情有点
slow
慢
so performance can be affected by it but
因此性能可能会受到影响，但
and it's not won by default you have to
而且默认情况下您不会赢
turn around explicitly and it only works
明确地转身，它只能工作
with g1 but besides that I think it's
与g1，但除此之外，我认为这是
pretty cool now in terms been with us
就我们而言，现在很酷
for a long time and what in turn does is
长期以来，反过来是
it gives you a strength from the shade
它从阴影中带给您力量
string table and we Dimitra now I gave a
字符串表，我们Dimitra现在我给了
talk at JavaOne Ostia cut a code one
在JavaOne上的演讲Ostia削减了一个代码
called cold one and at code one we gave
叫做冷一，我们给的代码一
a talk and we lied to the people but we
谈话，我们对人民撒谎，但我们
didn't do on purpose you know because
你不是故意的，因为
they changed something in Java livin
他们用Java livin改变了一些东西
without telling anybody we still haven't
不告诉任何人我们还没有
figured out a way they actually did that
想出了他们实际做到的方式
or way they they document that what they
或他们记录下来的方式
were doing but what did it was some
在做，但那是什么
driver live and they changed whether the
司机住了，他们改变了是否
intern table is structured up until Java
直到Java为止，构造实习表
Tim the intern table was was was a fixed
蒂姆实习生的桌子是固定的
sized table and was always a prime
大小的桌子，总是素数
number you know that all the the typical
你知道所有典型的数字
hashing magic they and their changed it
哈希魔术他们和他们改变了
in Java eleven to be changing seven and
在Java 11中要更改7
also power of two so it starts within
也是二的幂，所以它开始于
65,000 you know and then it keeps on
您知道65,000，然后持续下去
growing as you add more more strings in
随着您添加更多字符串而增长
order to reduce the amount the the
为了减少数量
mountain above caches that you have
您拥有的缓存之上的山脉
inside the hashmap
在哈希图中
inside the string table so the
在字符串表中，所以
performance is still not great for the
性能仍然不是很好
intern table it's it's you can get much
实习表是你可以获得很多
better performance if you if you make
如果您做得更好的性能
your own for example concurrent hash map
您自己的并发哈希图
and use that to to stall duplicates of
并用它来阻止重复的
strings but it's it's not as bad as it
字符串，但这不是那么糟糕
used to be
以前是
prior to Java travel if it's a java java
Java旅行之前，如果它是java java
level it's not change this but and drop
水平这不是改变它，而是下降
a 12 is the same as 12 11 and what's
12与12 11相同，这是什么
changed okay the because identification
改好了，因为识别
will save some memory because you're not
将节省一些内存，因为您不在
deduplicating in the torah but of course
在torah中进行重复数据删除，但当然
if you if you've got a
如果你有一个
a complete if you intern or concurrent
完整的，如果您是实习生或并发
hash map it will actually be using
它将实际使用的哈希图
saving even more memory no other to you
为您节省更多的内存
I'll talk about the structure beauty
我会说说结构美
we'll talk about the the results or
我们将讨论结果或
effects of the this job and I'm they
这项工作的影响，我是
changed the battery I'm sure you've
换了电池，我确定你已经
heard that they're also got a coded by a
听说他们也有一个
coda bite to say what the encoding is if
柯达咬一口说什么是编码
its YouTube you know if it's YouTube
它的YouTube您知道它是否是YouTube
sixteen or utf-16 or or latin-1 that's
十六或utf-16或latin-1
right they don't like the Greeks anyone
对，他们不喜欢希腊人
lerton one um and they're also changed
勒顿一嗯，他们也改变了
the way that they that they do the
他们做事的方式
string concatenation is remember when
记住字符串串联
we're in front of four to five we had to
我们在四到五个的前面
recompile all our code and this means
重新编译我们所有的代码，这意味着
that and the way that build things the
以及构建事物的方式
past they couldn't optimize the curtain
过去他们无法优化窗帘
had been compiled already by change of
已经通过更改而被编译
the algorithm and I think now it's
算法，我想现在是
definitely over to Dimitri so we did a
绝对是Dimitri，所以我们做了一个
little wrote little benchmark to to show
很少写一点基准来显示
how these things affect the code so what
这些东西如何影响代码呢？
you see on the screen we we have a
您在屏幕上看到的是
benchmark where we add together strings
我们将字符串加在一起的基准
with a plus with string builder in Java
Java中带有字符串构建器的加号
5 onwards using a string concatenated by
5起，使用由串联的字符串
the way that exists and stream for
存在和流向的方式
format and what you see like across the
格式以及整个画面
versions 6 7 &amp; 8 more or less always a
版本6 7和8或多或少总是
string builder was winning or rather
字符串生成器获胜还是宁可
plus and stringbuilder size tape the
加和stringbuilder大小的磁带
plus a string builder is the same
再加上一个字符串生成器是一样的
because that's exactly what java c would
因为那正是java c
emit so if you'd run write a plus 5 the
发射，所以如果您要编写加号5
code we generated new string builder
我们生成新的字符串生成器的代码
append a append 5 so that's why plus is
追加一个追加5，这就是为什么加号是
doing billy the same and if you knew the
做比利一样，如果你知道
size of the string upfront so string in
前期字符串的大小，因此输入
size that was always faster now if you
尺寸现在总是更快
switch and you look to java 11 then the
切换，然后您查看Java 11，然后
plus actually wins wins big deal and
加上实际获胜会赢得大笔交易，
especially if you look when moment of
特别是当你看的时候
bytes allocated
分配的字节
so exactly here you see an interplay of
所以恰恰在这里，您会看到
two features one is compact strings you
两个特点之一是紧凑的琴弦
remember in Java six they added byte
记得在Java中，六位他们增加了字节
array char erasing that there was a
数组字符擦除了一个
special flag it was retired somewhere
特别标志，它在某处退休了
between seven and eight because they
在七到八点之间，因为他们
realized it was not such a good good
意识到那不是很好
idea but what they also realized is that
想法，但他们也意识到的是
if you analyze the heap dance in general
如果您一般分析堆舞
lots of stuff about 25% of things in new
大约有25％的新事物
Java hits as strings and majority of the
Java命中字符串和大多数
strings are letting one encoded so it's
字符串让一个编码，所以
basically ASCII plus plus letting one
基本上是ASCII加加让一个
couple more characters but the the thing
几个更多的字符，但事情
with Latin once-through was letting one
与拉丁语一路走来
character said it fits in one bite Java
角色说它适合一口食
used to have strings always utf-16
以前总是有字符串utf-16
encoded which means need two bytes
编码，这意味着需要两个字节
that's why we had character array so
这就是为什么我们要使用字符数组
with Java nine plus that is replaced so
与Java九加，所以被替换
even on the Java source there is no more
即使在Java源代码上也没有更多
character array it's always by three
字符数组总是三
which brings a couple of interesting
这带来了一些有趣的
things if we go on just the quiz not
如果我们只是进行测验而没有
asked me us at the beginning was a bit
一开始问我我们有点
different to this benchmark because
不同于此基准，因为
there in the quiz we only appended
在测验中，我们只附加了
strings together and in this benchmark
在这个基准中串在一起
we mix parameters we had some inter
我们混合了一些参数
think implants int long double I think I
我认为我的植入物长两倍
don't double but at least we have we had
不要加倍，但至少我们有
some numbers and some strings together
一些数字和一些串在一起
and when you when you makes you the
当你让你
parameters then it does make a
参数然后它确实使
difference if using plus or
使用加号或加号的区别
stringbuilder sized or string bold then
然后将stringbuilder大小或字符串加粗
it actually does make a difference I
实际上确实有所作为
just want to mention one more thing if
只想再说一件事，如果
you look at the string format down there
你看那里的字符串格式
it's just horrible it's like 15 times so
简直太可怕了15次
15 X loses two to the plus well all is
15 X加2赔全是
not lost there is a Jap three four eight
不输有一个日本三四八
and currently in candidate state is not
目前处于候选状态
slated for any job release yet but what
计划发布任何职位，但是
do you want to do they want to enter in
你想做他们想输入吗
safai the string format so essentially
safai如此本质上的字符串格式
turning string format call into
将字符串格式调用转换为
something like string concatenation
类似于字符串连接
because the problem string format is
因为问题字符串格式是
that first to get the format string
首先获取格式字符串
which you need to parse to see where the
您需要解析以查看
armies are the arguments that you pass
军队是你传递的论点
to string format need to be boxed into
字符串格式需要装箱
objects the array needs to be allocated
需要分配数组的对象
and there's a lot of overhead and for
而且有很多开销，
example stinking card now can take
现在可以使用示例臭味卡
advantage and do stuff without
优势，做事没有
allocating objects
分配对象
can you talk about it late so a string
你能不能这么晚谈一谈
concatenation starting with JDK nine
从JDK九开始串联
Jeff 280 as Heinz mentioned the problem
杰夫280（Heinz）提到了问题
string concatenation it was a Java C
字符串连接，这是一个Java C
feature so every time you compiled code
功能，因此每次您编译代码时
Java C will emit bytecode and the Jade
Java C将发出字节码，而Jade
would have to live with that bytecode
将不得不使用该字节码
for error so they try to optimize
错误，因此他们尝试优化
certain things they did a lot of stuff
他们做了很多事情
then they realize there is too much
然后他们意识到太多了
effort to support JIT to have optimized
努力支持JIT进行优化
strings so what if we do something
字符串，如果我们做某事怎么办
different
不同
what if you compile strings to a point
如果将字符串编译到某一点怎么办
which we made different bytecode and let
我们制作了不同的字节码，然后让
the VM optimize it so starting with JDK
VM对其进行了优化，因此从JDK开始
nine actually if you do have a site
如果您确实有一个站点，那么九点
about Java P output and how this compile
关于Java P输出以及如何编译
okay anyways so what what happens is the
好吧，那么发生了什么
bytecode levels so if you compile so
字节码级别，所以如果您这样编译
first of all you would have to recompile
首先，您必须重新编译
the code you would not be able to take
您将无法使用的代码
advantage of new string concatenation
新字符串连接的优点
unless you compile with let's say with
除非您与一起编译
Java 11 so what would happen is that you
Java 11所以会发生的是你
would have invoked dynamic instruction
本来会调用动态指令
emitted in the code and invoke invoke
在代码中发出并调用invoke
dynamic for those of you who doesn't
对于那些没有动力的人
know is basically like it's a two-stage
知道基本上是两个阶段
process so when it's getting cold it
过程，所以当它变冷时
first needs to call the bootstrap method
首先需要调用bootstrap方法
to know what do I need to do the booster
知道我需要做些什么
pettite returns at the call side and
身材娇小的人在召唤侧返回，
from now on it will always call this
从现在开始，它将始终称为
call side so they basically use a
通话方，因此他们基本上使用
feature that was added originally for
最初为以下功能添加的功能
dynamic languages that was later on used
后来使用的动态语言
from Java 8 for lambdas and now in
从Java 8 for lambdas到现在
general 9 we use it also for student
一般9我们也将它用于学生
catenation so this thing is getting more
串联，所以这个东西越来越多
and more used throughout vm and she
在整个vm中使用得更多，她
actually brings two superpowers if you
实际上带来了两个超级大国
look inside of the actual bootstrap
看看实际的引导程序
implementation there is a string called
实现中有一个字符串叫做
card factory in in jdk angel on there is
在jdk天使卡厂上有
actually six different strategies to
实际上有六种不同的策略
concatenate strings so that roughly two
连接字符串，以便大约两个
groups one is the bytecode generated
第一组是生成的字节码
based on the string builder so it's
基于字符串生成器，因此
basically byte code to generate string
基本上是字节码来生成字符串
build like it was before or it uses the
像以前一样构建或使用
method handles all the way down and
方法一直向下处理
there are different variations where
有不同的变化
they all use string builder but the
他们都使用字符串生成器，但是
default one is different so the default
默认值不同，因此默认值
one is not allocated string builder at
一个未分配的字符串生成器位于
all
所有
so what they do instead they say okay
所以他们做什么，他们说没关系
you're concatenated something what at
你被串联在什么东西
the end you gonna create a string string
最后你要创建一个字符串
that I have a byte array so why not we
我有一个字节数组，所以为什么不
just allocate the byte array and write
只是分配字节数组并写入
bytes into the back right array and when
个字节放入右后数组以及何时
they create a string they will share the
他们创建一个字符串，他们将共享
byte array with a string so there will
具有字符串的字节数组，因此将
be no extra purpose whatever so the
没什么特别的目的
numbers you saw there like 150 bytes on
您在那里看到的数字大约为150个字节
whatever that's exactly number of bytes
无论是多少字节
that pankot needs to do this is not a
Pankot需要执行此操作不是
single byte wasted when I find it pretty
当我觉得漂亮的时候浪费了一个字节
awesome this and we have now and
太棒了，我们现在有
benchmark two to show the difference
基准二显示差异
between the things you see the default
您看到的默认值之间
one is the fastest and then we have
一个是最快的，然后我们有
different variations of wins but I don't
胜利的不同变化，但我没有
know who would ever change the
知道谁会改变
concatenation structure it's probably
串联结构
just like a kill switch so you can if it
就像一个消灭开关，所以你可以
has a bug so you have an option to you
有一个错误，所以您可以选择
know fix the bug without installing the
知道修复错误，而无需安装
new right so now back to the divide
新权利，现在回到鸿沟
thing so as I explained about
正如我所解释的
compressing char to legend one and there
将char压缩为图例一
is a kill switch compact strings which
是一个扼杀开关紧凑的弦，
you can disable that and it should it's
您可以禁用它，应该
interesting during development they had
在开发过程中他们很有趣
a bit catch-22 problem because compact
有点catch-22问题，因为紧凑
strings is a common line flag and common
字符串是常见的行标志，并且很常见
line flags are strings now you are
行标志是字符串，现在你是
inside a string class and you need to
在字符串类中，您需要
look to look up a common line flag so
看起来要查找公共线标志，因此
that doesn't work so they had to do
那行不通，所以他们不得不做
something really weird to be able to
真的很奇怪
solve the problem where they have a
解决他们有一个问题
constant which is not a constant that is
常数，不是常数
replaced by VM because there is no other
被VM取代，因为没有其他
way of doing it they try to use unsafe
他们尝试使用不安全的方式
and everything else but the string is so
除字符串外，其他所有内容都是如此
important to JVM startup that if we just
对于JVM启动很重要，如果我们只是
crush we am every time they did try
暗恋我们每次他们尝试
different things if you understand more
如果您了解更多，就会有所不同
look up
抬头
Alex's ship let's talk on that he goes
亚历克斯的船让我们谈谈他的去向
to detail how they fight the VM to just
详细说明他们如何与虚拟机抗争
have something like this stupid flag so
有这样的愚蠢的标志，所以
now it is back back to our benchmark and
现在又回到了我们的基准
just the fact of having or not having
有或没有的事实
compact strings and if you see and the
紧凑的字符串，如果您看到和
plus up there we see the difference in
再加上那里，我们看到了区别
the bytes allocated if the strings are
如果字符串是
compacted or compact it's not exactly 2x
压缩或压缩不完全是2倍
you would think because string object
你会认为因为字符串对象
has you know pointers to the array and
你知道数组的指针吗？
hash code and other stuff
哈希码和其他东西
other things around it but and the more
它周围的其他东西，以及更多
memories allocated i wanna quickly
记忆分配给我，我想快速
button and say there's this to me feels
按钮并说有这个对我来说
but Fulks bargain ish because some case
但福尔克人讨价还价是因为有些情况
I've made I've done seemed to him to
我让我觉得自己完成了
indicate that it actually does make a
表明它确实使
difference of performance if it's at
性能差异
least versus between Java 8 2009 with
最少，而Java 8 2009与
having these compact strings that record
这些紧凑的琴弦记录着
optimize as much but so far we haven't
优化很多，但到目前为止我们还没有
been able to write the benchmark we
能够写出基准
tried quite hard to write benchmark two
尽力编写基准测试二
to prove that it is a problem in Java 9
证明这是Java 9中的问题
but it's almost like you know somehow
但几乎就像你知道
there's something going on that to
发生了什么事
figure out that we're testing it I don't
弄清楚我们正在测试它，我没有
know
知道
you know admission testing is going on
你知道入学考试正在进行中
there are some interesting edge cases
有一些有趣的边缘情况
first edge case is the maximum size of
第一种情况是最大尺寸
the string so if in JDK 8 you allocate
字符串，因此如果在JDK 8中分配
essentially you can say a new character
基本上你可以说一个新角色
array integer max value -2 that's a
数组整数最大值-2，即
maximum array size in Java you can
您可以使用Java中的最大数组大小
create a string of that size so it's 2
创建一个大小为2的字符串
billion elements array well in gdk9 plus
gdk9 plus中的十亿个元素排列良好
you can't because you have a byte array
你不能，因为你有一个字节数组
so it's still 2 billion elements of
所以它仍然是20亿个元素
bytes and now here's the trick if your
个字节，如果您的
string is compressible you can do that
字符串是可压缩的，你可以这样做
your code will work if your string is
如果您的字符串是
utf-16 string you need twice twice the
utf-16字符串，您需要两次两次
size of the array array is half of it
数组的大小是数组的一半
you will get and finally out of memory
你会得到，最终内存不足
error saying you cannot allocate that
错误，说你不能分配
big of a string and it gives you 1
大串，它给你1
billion during the max value can be
最大值可以是十亿
that's first thing and second thing and
那是第一件事，第二件事，
certain operations like substring and
某些操作，例如子串和
other stuff might get into trouble
其他东西可能会惹上麻烦
because you're walking a like when you
因为当你走路时就像
for instance go from compressed and
例如从压缩和
uncompressed things but I'm getting too
未压缩的东西，但我也越来越
much into let's talk about intrinsic ok
让我们来谈谈内在的确定
yes
是
so another thing if you look at strings
还有另一件事，如果你看着琴弦
and Java coding in general there is this
和Java编码一般都有这个
thing called intrinsic so certain
所谓内在的东西肯定
operations in Java and you see that
Java中的操作，您会看到
there is a Java code for them but it's
他们有一个Java代码，但是
actually not what a JVM is executing if
实际上不是JVM在执行什么
you run them this is just a list of some
您运行它们，这只是一些列表
of spring related intrinsic sin and JDK
与春天有关的内在罪过和JDK
8 and if you look at 11 it's far more
8，而如果看11，则远远不止这些
well the reason we basically doubled all
好吧，我们基本上翻了一番的原因
the overhead of string working so before
字符串工作之前的开销
we just set one string class now inside
我们现在只在内部设置一个字符串类
there is like Latin one in utf-16 so we
在utf-16中有拉丁语，所以我们
double that and there were moment in
加倍，有片刻
this editor now there is another
这个编辑器现在还有另一个
interesting thing if you look on JDK 9
如果您看一下JDK 9，将会很有趣
plus how equals is implemented for
加上如何实现平等
example there is this this check at the
例如，此检查在
beginning and then if it's string first
开始，然后是字符串
thing they do they compare coda
他们做的事情他们比较尾声
so this is a special case if you have
所以这是一个特殊的情况
two strings of different encoding they
他们编码不同的两个字符串
by definition cannot be equal so this is
根据定义不能相等，所以这是
a short circuit inside ok if you compare
如果您比较，内部短路
strings that are not of the same
不相同的字符串
encoding we can skip that thing and then
编码我们可以跳过那件事，然后
they check what is the common encoding
他们检查什么是通用编码
called one of these methods so to make a
称为这些方法之一，以便使
point about intrinsic let's look at how
关于内在的观点让我们看一下如何
one of this methods is implemented like
这种方法之一是像
letting 1 equals so basically we just
让1等于所以基本上我们只是
walk the array element by element if you
如果您逐个数组元素
find that any unequal will stop
发现任何不平等都会停止
otherwise we have to walk all the all
否则我们必须全部走
the area to the end see this little
到尽头的区域看到这一点
annotation hotspot intrinsic candidate
注解热点内在候选
it tells the VM that this code should be
它告诉VM该代码应为
potentially replaced with something else
可能被其他东西取代
if the something else works on this
如果其他东西可以解决这个问题
particular platform so this is platform
特定的平台，所以这是平台
dependent and some other things come
依赖和其他一些事情来了
into play and yeah we the reason we show
发挥作用，是的，我们展示我们的理由
the RS mismatch this like did yet
RS不匹配，就像这样
another way to do that starting with jdk
从jdk开始的另一种方法
9 so let's let's measure the performance
9让我们评估一下性能
so if we call string equals with
所以如果我们用
different length of the strings it's
字符串的不同长度
basically made fast right it's close
基本上很快就快到了
linearly was so string but it's fast if
线性是如此字符串，但如果
we do it manually like they did it then
我们像他们那样手动进行
they like working the array manually you
他们喜欢手动操作阵列
see that it degrades way faster so we
看到它降解的速度更快，所以我们
have some performance problem and if you
有一些性能问题，如果您
use some new arrays mismatch stuff
使用一些新的数组不匹配的东西
it's almost as close to string equals
它几乎等于字符串等于
them so what we see in the play is
他们，所以我们在剧中看到的是
actually the intrinsic so the code that
实际上是内在的，所以代码
we we saw on the screen we copied it and
我们在屏幕上看到了我们复制的内容，
try to run that but it's not sure it's
尝试运行它，但不能确定
not the coldest thing equals is using
不是最冷的东西正在使用
the code is replaced was a vectorized
代码被替换为矢量化
loop essentially instead of walking
循环而不是步行
every element at a time one byte they
每个元素一次一个字节
walk eight bytes in strides of eight
大步走八个字节
bytes so you basically get the chunks
字节，因此您基本上可以获得块
and you he goes from memory foster yes
而你他从记忆中成长
so the one thing which is interesting is
所以有趣的一件事是
that they don't actually take you can't
他们实际上不带你不能
for deduplication right so the in the
对于重复数据删除权，所以在
equals they it would make sense to see
等于他们有道理
all this other areas the same there is
所有其他区域都一样
the same instance you can see return
您可以看到相同的实例返回
true in the current string structure so
在当前字符串结构中为true
that would speed things up if you're
如果您是
comparing equal strings there's a few
比较相等的字符串有一些
lessons from today um use plus and set
今天的教训um使用plus和set
of string builder wherever possible and
尽可能使用字符串生成器
you'd have to recompile your code to
您必须重新编译代码以
take advantage of the opportunity Chazz
把握机会Chazz
we've got there also if you're gonna use
如果您要使用我们也可以到达那里
if you isn't turning your code and I've
如果你不把你的代码，我已经
seen the same code bases where they are
看到了相同的代码库
used in turn extensively rather see if
反过来广泛使用而不是看看
you use your own cache because it can be
您使用自己的缓存，因为它可以
many factors faster even with an
即使使用
improved Java Devon version we found it
我们找到了改进的Java Devon版本
to be in a many many factors faster to
更快地进入许多因素
be to use your own concurrent hash map
使用您自己的并发哈希图
for especially return of too many
特别是太多的回报
strings it can make big difference how
字符串可以有很大的不同
she can be expensive on strings
她的琴弦可能很贵
especially if the hash resolves to zero
特别是如果哈希解析为零
and there's not much they can do about
而且他们无能为力
that
那
you know they can't change the default
你知道他们不能改变默认值
value of hash because that would produce
哈希值，因为这会产生
a data race on the string itself which
字符串本身的数据竞争
we've quite dangerous to have doing
我们这样做很危险
absolutely cannot have a dangerous data
绝对不能有危险数据
rate happen and also since over nine
发生率也超过了九
we've had byte arrays for Strings not
我们没有字符串的字节数组
Charlie's just remember when you're
查理只是记得你什么时候
looking at your at your profiling that
看着你的个人资料
you're looking for byte arrays for
您正在寻找字节数组
Strings not Charles since Java nine
自Java九以来字符串不查尔斯
onwards we've got the the benchmarks on
以后我们就已经有了基准
our on my on my github carpet string
我们在我的github地毯上
performance and you mother welcome to to
表演，你妈妈欢迎参加
comment and to run the taste this off
发表评论并尝试一下
and try and break as much as you can
并尽力打破
always happy for feedback
总是很高兴获得反馈
is what one last thing which was quite
最后一件事是什么
interesting with intrinsics
有趣的内在函数
just a weird puzzle so Intel had a
只是一个奇怪的难题，所以英特尔有一个
machine at inter other performance
除其他性能外的机器
course the end and are often attributed
当然结束，通常被认为是
machine way sometimes the the equals
机器方法有时等于
method now sometimes the the compare to
方法现在有时与
method would come back with zero on on
方法将以零打开
two different strings so two different
两个不同的字符串，所以两个不同
strings on that one machine would
一台机器上的字符串会
sometimes give back 0 when it was two
有时在两岁时还给0
different strings okay and and we we
不同的字符串还可以，我们
actually got it down to a race condition
实际上是将其归结为比赛条件
between intrinsics and and and and the
内在和与和与之间
normal you know interpreted code way it
通常你知道解释代码的方式
and when they turned off intrinsics
当他们关闭内在函数时
this was a very specific version of Java
这是Java的非常特定的版本
eight running on a very very specific
八个非常具体地运行
machine so it could have been a hard way
机器，所以本来很难
back quite quite possibly because then
回到很可能是因为
they're upgraded the hard way and that
他们已经艰难地升级了
bug went away so we can never reproduce
错误消失了，所以我们永远都无法繁殖
it again there's quite quite a funny
再次有一个相当有趣的
little race conditioning so this is it
种族限制少，就这样
from us thanks much for listening thanks
来自我们，非常感谢您的收听谢谢
Dimitri and else if there is a surprise
迪米特里（Dimitri）和其他惊喜
if you go there if you don't well later
如果你以后不舒服就去那里
on there'll be another surprise on this
在这上会有另一个惊喜
deal thanks any questions we've got
谢谢我们有任何疑问
about there for four minutes for
大约在那里四分钟
questions
问题
lots of lots of time yes sir
很多时间，是的，先生
Java the-- we've got in Java 12 that's
Java-我们在Java 12中有了
not enough changes we've that we could
没有足够的变化，我们可以
attend so driver 12 is the same store
参加，所以司机12是同一家商店
whatever they've got these these are
不管他们有这些这些
what are called the strings one is the
所谓的字符串之一是
string literals where you can you know
您知道的字符串文字
like have three quotes open and then
像打开三个引号，然后
write free-floating thing that's gonna
写自由浮动的东西
happen and bunch of methods that relate
发生和一系列相关的方法
to that when we don't know maybe 13
当我们不知道也许13
maybe not they pushed it out of 12 so
也许不是他们将其从12中推出
that might come other one is the string
可能是另一个字符串
format and the original object objects
格式和原始对象对象
hash code that's the the amber stuff as
哈希代码是琥珀色的东西
I said there is jab three four eight
我说有刺戳三四八
candidate state it's not slated for
候选国家（未定）
release so that's another thing that has
发布，这是另一件事
gonna happen and but other than that
将会发生，但除此之外
string specific guys I don't know so
字符串特定的家伙，我不知道
there's two things I mean the changes as
我指的是两件事
you know from Java cemetery we're quite
你知道从Java公墓
dramatic and drop eighty-nine squatter
戏剧性和下降八十九个棚户区
met nowadays it's like you know every
如今相遇，就像你知道每一个
half a year but the change is not it's
半年，但变化不是
not as big impact anymore so I don't I'm
不再有那么大的影响，所以我不
not sure what they'll do is anybody
不知道他们会做什么
using something other than eight like
使用八点以外的东西
this obviously obviously cartoons Java 8
这显然是卡通Java 8
introduction safely anymore I don't
不再安全地介绍我
think
认为
[Applause]
[掌声]